Revenge is a dirty business.
Clean is a crime, action, drama film directed by Paul Solet.
Tormented by a past life, garbage man Clean attempts a life of quiet redemption.
But when his good intentions mark him a target of a local crime boss,
Clean is forced to reconcile with the violence of his past.
Clean, played by Adrien Brody.
Michael, played by Glenn Fleshler.
Mikey, played by Richie Merritt.
Dianda, played by Chandler DuPont.
Travis, played by Mykelti Williamson.
Ethel, played by Michelle Wilson.
Clean is an Australian 2022 documentary film about the life of Sandra Pankhurst, a transgender
woman who became best known for her work as a crime scene and trauma cleaner.
The film centres on Pankhurst's journey from a difficult upbringing—which included adoption and an
eventual teenage eviction—to her marriage and experiences with gender identity.
The film follows Pankhurst's early struggles with the eventual establishment of Specialist Trauma Cleaning Services, which has a
team of cleaners who clean crime scenes, places where people have committed suicide, and incidents of hoarding.
Pankhurst attends and leads jobs with her team while sharing her experiences and
challenges of the industry as well as showcasing the nature of her profession.
As the film progresses, Pankhurst's health declines, possibly
due to extended exposure to cleaning substances.
Nevertheless, she continues with her work and actively
participates in public speaking engagements.
The cast includes Pankhurst, who plays herself, and her employees.
The film was produced by David Elliot-Jones and Charlotte Wheaton of Walking Fish Productions and directed
by Lachlan Mcleod who had been inspired by Pankhurst's story after seeing her on television.
Clean was released in 2022.
The film was screened at the Melbourne International Film
Festival and the Edinburgh International Film Festival.
It was nominated for two awards at the Australian Academy of
Cinema and Television Arts Awards in 2022.
Audiences and critics received Clean well.
The film explores themes of new york city,
garbageman , gangster, drug use, revenge.
The tone is emotional.